# **Austin Baxley**

Atlanta, Georgia, United States AusBaxley@gmail.com 678-435-3558 in/abaxley2 https://github.com/abaxley2

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, maintaining, and building websites and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript and have experience with using MySQL, NoSQL, Node.js, and React. Also experienced with MongoDB, Express, and Handlebars.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Restaurant Manager**

# Tin Lizzy's Cantina

January 2020 - May 2021, Kennesaw, GA

- · Launched new product offerings.
- Managed a large and intricate inventory of product and ordered product to fill any gaps.
- · Managed a large and diverse team and wrote all scheduling.

#### **Band Director**

## **Cobb County Schools**

September 2013 - May 2016, Marietta, GA

- · Developed curriculum and conducted clinics to enable students to learn in an adaptable setting.
- · Performed and organized at over 40 performances including concerts, festivals, and parades.
- Instructed and maintained a group of over 400 students each year.

## **Restaurant Manager**

# **CentraArchy Restaurant Management Group**

March 2013 - December 2019, Atlanta, GA

- · Sourced, developed, and trained new restaurant managers.
- Increased key metrics including guest counts, revenue per guest.
- · Increased overall revenue by 15%.

# **PROJECTS**

# **Regex Tutorial**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · August 2021

- · Developed a working tutorial on Regular Expressions.
- · Explained in detail each aspect of Regex and it's applicable use.
- · Successfully deployed a GitHub Gist.
- · GitHub Gist: https://gist.github.com/abaxley2/a796040212cdac792dc67c286ba42a41

## **Get Money Smart**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp • July 2021

- · Created a mobile-responsive banking web application as a tool for teachers.
- · Created and tested API routes.
- · Successfully deployed application to Heroku.
- · GitHub Link: https://github.com/mlward639/Get Money Smart
- · Deployed Link: https://polar-river-76787.herokuapp.com/

## **Market Finder**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · June 2021

- · Created a web application that used third party APIs to locate local farmer's markets by location.
- · Wrote and managed project assignments.
- · Successfully deployed the application through GitHub.
- · GitHub Link: https://github.com/abaxley2/Market-Finder
- · Deployed Link: https://abaxley2.github.io/Market-Finder/

## **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor's of Music in Music Education

# **SKILLS**

Technical Skills: Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Nodejs, React Js, Node Jsexperience, Bootstrap, Express, Mongoose, Graphql Apollo, MVC, Webapi, Mongo Db, Nosql, MySQL